Guide to the Festival of Black Gospel records, 1982-2007.
Festival of Black Gospel records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Festival of Black Gospel records, 1982-2007.
37-6-3678
Cornell University.Festival of Black Gospel.
1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, meeting minutes, programs, planning documents, and publicity concerning the Festival of Black Gospel.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The festival, a traditional part of Black History Month events at Cornell, is a Cornell student-led organization founded in 1976 by the late Rev. W. Jack Lewis, director of the Cornell United Religious Work.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, meeting minutes, programs, planning documents, and publicity concerning the Festival of Black Gospel.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Lewis, Jack.; Cornell University--Societies,etc.; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
Music--Societies,etc.; Cornell University--Students.; Minority college students--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Minorities--Education, Higher.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Photographs, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bylaws, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Next Step Program, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 7th Festival, Jun 1982- Feb 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 8th Festival, Jun 1983- Feb 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 9th Festival, Jun 1984- Feb 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 10th Festival, Jun 1985- Feb 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 11th Festival, Jun 1985- Feb 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos-12th Festival, Jun 1987- Feb 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 13th Festival, Jun 1988- Feb 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 14th Festival, Jun 1989- Feb 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 15th Festival, Apr 1990- Dec 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 15th Festival, Jn 1991- July 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 16th Festival, Jun 1991- Feb 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 17th Festival, Jun 1992- Feb 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 18th Festival, Jun 1993- Feb 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 19th Festival, Jun 1994- Feb 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 20th Festival, Jun 1995- Feb 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 21st Festival, Jun 1996- Feb 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 22nd Festival, Jun 1997- Feb 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 23rd Festival, Jun 1998- Feb 1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 24th Festival, Jun 1999- Feb 2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 25th Festival, Jun 2000- Feb 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 26th Festival, Jun 2001- Feb 2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 27th Festival, Jun 2002-Feb 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 28th Festival, Jun 2003- Feb 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Correspondences, Publicity, Contracts, Memos- 29th Festival, Jun 2004- Feb 2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Poster- 31st Festival (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1991-2008 (Box 1, Folder 29)